There it is!
I can see it!
Rush!
You’ve done well to
make it this far, Mega Man!
But it seems this is
where we part ways.
Now watch from the afterlife
as I conquer the world!
Farewell!
Rush!
Rush...
Are you okay?
You’re...!
My name is Duo.
I was created to eliminate
evil energy from the universe.
Here it comes.
Duo,
That’s the same from last time...
Yes.
In this planet’s terms,
it is called evil energy.
What I’ve discovered up until now
is that those who possess this
energy’s source harbor evil hearts.
This energy absorbs evil hearts
to create a physical form.
It’s still growing stronger…
If we don’t stop it soon, this planet
will be consumed by evil energy!
I can feel the energy’s
presence in that tower
However...
There’s a barrier in our way.
I’ll look for the remaining
energy and deal with it.
You go find the energy
source and destroy it.
Got it.
Let’s go, Rush!