Not good.
He’s being consumed by evil energy.
At this rate Mega Man will die.
If you haven’t been
consumed by evil energy yet,
this will save you.
Mega Man...
I can see within your heart…
You’ve been working this hard…
all for the sake of justice?
If you’re here,
then this planet is already safe.
What happened to Mega Man!?
He’s alright.
He’ll wake up soon.
My work here is done.
We probably won’t meet again.
I leave Mega Man to you.
I forgot one thing.
Sorry,
but I have a request.
Mega Man!
Stay strong, Mega Man!
Roll...
Mega Man!
Alright!
I’m alive.
Yes.
Duo saved you.
Duo...
If it’s about Duo, he already left.
Proto Man!
Mega Man, he entrusted
me with this message.
From Duo?
What is it?
He said, ‘Thank you.’
Duo...
Me too.
Thank you, Duo...